MATTHEW MARTIN

JUNIOR WEB DEVELOPER

CAREER OBJECTIVE

In 2020 I made the decision to change career paths from engineering to software development. Since then, I have developed a love for using my skills to problem solve and develop new projects. I hope to join a team where I can push myself further, gather experience and continue learning new skills.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Information Technology — Southern Cross University MAR 2020 - AUG 2022

Major: Software Development Current GPA: 6.85/7.0

Bachelor of Engineering — University of Newcastle

JUL 2013 - DEC 2019

Major: Civil

Graduated with Honours Class II Division I

SOFTWARE PROJECTS

Time Tracer — github.com/MatthewAMartin/time-tracer

A web application for capturing time records (against clients and projects) and dynamically generating invoices.

Languages & Technologies Used: HTML, CSS, JS, React, Next.js, Chakra UI, PostgreSQL, Supabase

Personal Portfolio — https://github.com/MatthewAMartin/matthew-portfolio My personal portfolio website with information about me, my skills and my

projects.

Languages & Technologies Used: HTML, CSS, JS, React, Next.is

The Cookie Artist — https://github.com/MatthewAMartin/TheCookieArtist
An in-development e-commerce website for 'The Cookie Artist' business.
Languages & Technologies Used: HTML, CSS, JS, React, Next.js, Node.js,
Express, MySQL, Bootstrap

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

English Tutoring Business Manager — Self-Employed, South Korea OCT 2020 - PRESENT

Real Estate Floor Planner — Self-Employed, Newcastle, Australia MAR 2016 - AUG 2020

Detailer (Industrial Exp.) — Liberty Reinforcing, Melbourne, Australia JUN 2018 - NOV 2018

DETAILS

AUS: +61 431 021 304
KOR: +82 010 9752 6186
mattmartin.2289@gmail.com
github.com/MatthewAMartin
linkedin.com/in/matthew-martin-a1
8356166/

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Front-End

HTML CSS JavaScript
Typescript React Next.js

Angular Chakra UI Bootstrap

Back-End

Node.js Express MySQL

PostgreSQL Supabase

Other

Java Systems Analysis & Design

Data Structures Algorithms

AWARDS

2021 Award for Academic Excellence (SCU) - GPA 6.6/7.0

2020 Award for Academic Excellence (SCU) - GPA 7.0/7.0

2017 Faculty Commendation List (UoN) - GPA 6.5+

LANGUAGES

English: Fluent Korean: Beginner